I want to read everybody some snippets
from the plot of the movie Terminator
Genesis. It doesn't have any relation to
anything that is going on today. It's
just very interesting and I think it's
important that everybody knows the plot
of this movie Terminator Genesis. So, in
the movie, Skynet is the original
artificial intelligence that becomes
self-aware and triggers judgment day.
Skynet then evolves and rebrands itself
as Genesis. Genesis is presented to the
public as a revolutionary benevolent
operating system that connects all
devices worldwide, phones, computers,
military systems, etc. into one unified
cloud-based platform, essentially the
ultimate smart system. Now, in the
movie, Skynet strategy is to achieve
singularity, not through a military
defense network. No. But, and here it
is, ladies and gentlemen, by disguising
itself as a consumer product that
everyone voluntarily connects to, making
resistance almost impossible once it
goes live. It also forced all people,
great and small, rich and poor, free and
slave to receive a mark on their right
hands or on their foreheads so that they
could not buy or sell h sounds like a
consumer product to me unless they had
the mark which is the name of the beast
or the number of its name. The Lord
Jesus Christ told us that the last days
would be like it was in the days of Noah
because the enemy is creating his own
version of mankind. He is creating his
own version of Eden. And that version of
mankind will connect to him through his
own version of the Holy Spirit. Even
though we don't see anything like this
movie plot in our real world, I wonder
just theoretically if we were to. I
wonder if people would go along with it
because it's cool and convenient and it
helped with their homework. I wonder if
people would root it on because of the
person that's coming out with it. I
wonder if they would be blind to what is
actually playing out right in front of
their eyes. Satan doesn't have any new
tricks. That's why we are circling back
to Genesis. So the same lie that was
told in the garden, ye shall be as gods,
will be the lie that will be told during
the tribulation. It will be his version
of eternity. And again, it will appease
to the flesh. It will appease to the
world. You can live forever. You can
have knowledge surpassing your wildest
dreams because now you're going to be
connected to the source of knowledge.
And for anybody who's unaware,
singularity refers to a hypothetical. So
don't worry guys, it's not real.
Nobody's talking about this future
point. When artificial intelligence
surpasses human intelligence, leading to
rapid and uncontrollable technological
growth, this scenario could maybe might
result in machines that could
autonomously improve themselves,
fundamentally transforming
human civilization in unpredictable
ways. It is Skynet's strategy to achieve
singularity, not through a military
defense network, but by disguising
itself as a consumer product that
everyone voluntarily connects to. Satan
is smart. He is clever and he is crafty.
And in these last days, we are going
back to Genesis and it will be the same
lie. Ye shall be as gods. I just have a
feeling that next year is going to be a
very interesting year. [music]